Had to or got to?
(Dave:)Sorry.
(Amy:)My fault. I brought him up.
Yeah.
(Dave:)Well, let's change the subject.
(Dave:)No more mentions
of you-know-who.
(laughs)
That's a cool train.
(Dave:)Where did you get that?
♪ Bah, bah, bum-bum,
bah, bum, bum. ♪
(humming tune)
(gargling song)
(Sheldon(singing):)This song
(Sheldon:)is never going to stop.
(Sheldon:)Have you ever dealt
with something
(Sheldon:)so relentlessly irritating?
(Leonard:)That's a trick
question, right?
(Sheldon:)Well, I shouldn't
be surprised.
(Sheldon:)There's a rich history of
(Sheldon:)brilliant minds
descending into madness.
PENNY:
Come on, Sheldon.
(Penny:)There are plenty of smart people
who don't have mental problems.
(Leonard:)Yup, she's right.
(Leonard:)For every Newton who had
a psychological issue,
(Leonard:)there's an Edison
who was just a jerk.
(Leonard:)That could
totally be you.
(Sheldon:)Empedocles thought he was a god
and jumped into a volcano.